//quiz question and answers

const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'What was the first Super Bowl appearance for the Eagles?',
    answers: [
      'Super Bowl I',
      'Super Bowl XV',
      'Super Bowl LII',
      'Super Bowl XXXIX',
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Super Bowl XV'
  },
  {
    question: 'What year did the Philadelphia Eagles begin playing in the NFL?',
    answers: [
      '1933',
      '1947',
      '1960',
      '1984',
      ],
    correctAnswer: '1933'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which famous Philadelphia Eagles player was known as "The Polish Rifle"?',
    answers: [
      'Randall Cunningham',
      'Ron Jaworski',
      'Steve Van Buren',
      'Chuck Bednarik',
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ron Jaworski'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the Eagles franchise All-time rushing record holder?',
    answers: [
      'Steve Van Buren',
      'Brian Westbrook',
      'Wilbert Montgomery',
      'LeSean McCoy',
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'LeSean McCoy'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the Eagles franchise All-time Scoring Leader?',
    answers: [
      'Michael Vick',
      'DeSean Jackson',
      'David Akers',
      'Harold Carmichael',
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'David Akers'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is Weapon X?',
    answers: [
      'Brian Dawkins',
      'Hugh Jackman',
      'Ryan Reynolds',
      'Logan Poole',
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Brian Dawkins'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which year did the Philadelphia Eagles beat Vince Lombardi for the NFL Championship?',
    answers: [
      '1958',
      '1959',
      '1960',
      '1961',
      ],
    correctAnswer: '1960'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Super Bowl did the Eagles win last?',
    answers: [
      'Super Bowl I',
      'Super Bowl XV',
      'Super Bowl LII',
      'Super Bowl XXXIX',
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Super Bowl LII'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Eagles player strip-sacked Tom Brady at the end of Super Bowl LII?',
    answers: [
      'Chris Long',
      'Brandon Graham',
      'Fletcher Cox',
      'Vinny Curry',
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Brandon Graham'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the only player in NFL history to throw and catch a touchdown in the Super Bowl?',
    answers: [
      'Nick Foles',
      'Tom "Butterfingers" Brady',
      'Danny "Should not throw the ball" Amendola',
      'Brandin "Never going to try to hurdle anyone again" Cooks',
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Nick Foles'
  }
  ];
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  